Alexander Fernandez

Full Stack Developer



- ♥ Villa Crespo, 1414 Buenos Aires, Argentina
 - alex97l@hotmail.com
 - **♦** 01121635165 **▶** Portfolio
- iii 26/02/1997 ► Argentinian **③** Single
 - in Linkedin 🖸 Github

Profile

Innovative and deadline-driven full stack developer with 5 year of experience designing and developing user-centered websites from initial concept to final.

Skills

Html / Css / Javascript (Jsx / Scss,

Ruby on Rails (Ruby / Irb)

Databases (Sql / PostgreSQL)

React (Node / Express / Redux

Package managers (Yarn / Npm)

Testing (Enzyme / Jest)

Professional Experience

Full Stack Developer, *Freelancer* 2022 – present | Buenos Aires, Argentina

In charge of Marketing & Supplies, Coto Cicsa

2017 - 2022 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

- I started as a cadet then was promoted and got in charge of shipments;
- Managed up to 234 shipments at the same time
- Consulted by clients when they had any trouble.
- Managed to lead 15 employees. In the third year, I was in charge of the marketing and supply section.

Courses

React course, *Udemy* ☑ 2022 – 2022 | Remote

Full Stack developer, Le Wagon ☑ 2021 – 2022 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Education

English

International Relations, Siglo XXI 2021 – present | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Software Engineer, *UBA*

2017 – 2020 | Buenos Aires, Argentina I started to program at the same time. Changed career before completing it.

Languages	
Coi-l-	
Spanish	